[Music]
blessings everyone Christian open the
rod vanish calm registered Holistic
Nutritionist raw food lifestyle coach
and raw chef
I'm here with whisper from unbound and
we're gonna make you alright so here we
are in lives kitchen here and we just
got this impromptu coconut kale noodle
salads a little bit of mangoes a lot of
different stuff and they're gonna get
into the ingredients to see what's up oh
and by the way I want to let you know
that you're gonna want to check out the
sister video that we make on lives
Channel this is gonna be another version
of what we're doing here it's a little
bit of different stuff it'll be a little
bit better than mine maybe something
you'll want to see alright so let's
check this off so what do we have here
we have beautiful kale you could use
different greens but we have beautiful
kale curly kale dinosaur kale we have
some spinach and we have some mustard
greens what's next we have some
beautiful mushrooms we have some 11 some
green onions some tumeric some sweet
pepper mangoes keep up coconut and
mature coconut plus ginger garlic hmm
alright so we're gonna start with these
beautiful little mushrooms and slice
them up and get them into hydrator so
the texture is just a little nice room
or juicy and succulent and delicious so
highly recommend the Excalibur
dehydrator which you can get on my
website up here yeah
Rafa shameless it's gonna put this in
here and a bowl
118 Fahrenheit or maybe 47 or 48 Celsius
for a half an hour to an hour depending
on what you want alternatively you could
also put in this Sun to boosted vitamin
D status or you could put them under
ultraviolet light a full spectrum light
no boost up that vitamin D status check
out my video above on vitamin D as a
vegan alright so next we're gonna chop
up this kale and for the newest and the
most efficient way possible I got a look
oh my god
[Music]
then we're gonna chemically cook the
kale this lemon
always cut towards yourself
[Music]
super secret technique sealed receipts
no problem
basically by putting some lemon in the
kale it becomes very soft and juicy
makes it taste even more salty who loves
that sodium
crystal nobody's helping his recipe
mm-hmm
I'm gonna look disapproving Lily at her
while she was herself happy hiking pants
off
it smells like
until it
now massage investigator
Queen it is it the secret making it nice
and soft not the chooses to come out now
yeah sharp nails I think you cut me I'm
doing your channels went to iron no
that's just when I came in oh really
lickings always love my videos Wow
becoming some stuff just like your
whispers mini history
then we're gonna chop up the spinach and
add it last
Olivia popped open the coconut reserve
the water for the sausage no no fat
jelly so you take the meat out we're
gonna be using this for the noodles and
the sauce catch you can you please bring
this outside keep thank you
all right so now it's time to make the
coconut milk so we're going to take this
mature coconut and you see there's three
eyes the biggest eye they looks like the
mouth like oh then you take the
corkscrew or a sharp knife just and if
you can you can get another one that'll
make it flow faster but it will still
come out just one the water
you always want to taste just a little
bit to make sure that it's not funky
right and if it's for you and someone
else has a bright line it's good okay so
we're gonna get this stuff off here oh
that's this the best when it works like
that
and we'll put all of that in the blender
to make this mature coconut milk and
into the fabulous Vitamix blender
Vitamix Vitamix Vitamix hurry up I on my
website the best price free shipping
seven-year warranty Vitamix Vitamix
Vitamix shameless and now I'm going to
make some coconut water with the coconut
meat with a mature coconut me a little
bit more Nikki nice baking and saucy
oh that should be enough Wow so this
should be nice and smooth and that we
can us to Train it to it
okay little nut milk bag or some
cheesecloth avoid using a spatula at all
costs it's just another thing to wash
careful those nails oh oh
squirting on me ginger
the power of the Vitamix you don't even
have to peel it
do you Marik
garlic no peeling Wow Oh medium mild or
hot pepper
mango
if you'd like to see how to eat a mango
without knife then go to my channel I
just made a video about how to eat mango
with no mess ya know guys you need to go
to see my video about the mango so we're
gonna put all the mangoes in here hmmm
that looks so good it kind of looks like
me oh this is so satisfying it's good
right so satisfying I don't think I'll
ever use a knife again so some of this
coconut jelly for thickening and some
for noodles the younger jellies for
thickening and will use the bigger one
the medium one for noodles now we have
all this yumminess right here and we're
going to put it back in the Vitamix
it should be not let's see it matches
your dress oh my god I can't even
describe how this smells so amazing is
it good wow wow wow this is so good
so let's pour this over all the green
stuff that you feel better before whoa
we like a saucy right this is so saucy I
like to do better yourself think
associate the better the saucier the
better so now we have all the greens or
the curry sauce and we leave it marinate
for just few minutes are we preparing
the mushrooms and the coconut noodles
yes yes yes they're not working at all
mmm and now I'm going to make some
coconut milk I wish I had the coconut
noodle maker but I don't
it's okay I'm going to use the knife and
all I'm gonna do with a soft coconut
she's about the medium softness just
gonna slice tiny little noodles
it's like fettuccine fettuccine with
some stuff in it
pata pata Cheney is it fatty tini
coconut fettuccine mm-hmm I love coconut
noodles oh okay hi these noodles be
happier
right
I'm gonna put them straight in the car
let's make some more going to put all in
sides is it there yet it's in the
mushroom interrelations now slightly
crispy and slightly juicy inside just
the texture is better than just gently
putting them all inside always gently of
mushrooms always implicit sorry this is
it is basically mango kale coconut bliss
curry mushrooms is gonna be bliss
oh my I can't wait Oh
- you made sure trying alright I wanna
make sure that I want to have like a
mushroom noodle and a kale in laughing
the bite I just I just I didn't want
anything
hmm you'll do I was planning to put some
salt in my one because the criticism you
solve this doesn't need salt at all
[Music]
hmm
I think the mushrooms like all of it
actually I mean the sauce you guys want
to watch just eat the whole thing
hope you guys absolutely love it make
sure you like comment and subscribe to
both of us here hey mm-hmm as always
wishing you much peace 11 seasonal fruit
legally good news insane I have one the
head alone when no like so ready
try this one this is the best I love bra
curry coconut kale mango glaze curry who
don't forget check out my bra recipes
playlist in the top left the video just
for you in the top rate subscribe and
the bottom writing your read books in
the bottom left hang check Olivia Chows
- all in from the description below grab
my free iPhone app comes with 50 free
recipes common fruit vegetable carrier
break down food combining chart shopping
cart function and much much more